(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T22:26:24.255960",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
愛しいの
My beloved...
ただ触れて抱きしめていたいような時
Times when I just want to touch and hold you close...
暗い夜の底で
At the bottom of a dark night,
少し楽しいね なんてね
"It's a little fun, isn't it?" Just kidding...
超電波バスターズ 巡ってまるごと関わると
Super Radio Wave Busters! Spinning around and getting fully involved,
空の彼方へ
to beyond the sky...
ててててのれ 超電波バスターズ
Te-te-te-te-no-re, Super Radio Wave Busters!
大春 鳴らせてる 胸踊るスパ銀河の音
Ringing in the grand spring, heart-thrilling super galaxy sounds!
アバンチュラリラリ 8光年先の未来 誰もが求めるウェーブの音
Aventura-ri-ra-ri! A future 8 light-years away, the sound of the wave everyone seeks!
3次元でドンジット 地球上そてててて なんどちみたスターロジャーで
Don-jit in 3D! On Earth, te-te-te-te, with Star Roger that we've seen so many times!
アバンチュラリラリ 8000年時代はグルグルまわり
Aventura-ri-ra-ri! An era of 8000 years spinning round and round,
宇宙はパズルメカ 時代と同期して
The universe is a puzzle mech, synchronizing with the era.
さあ 次の波へ
Come on, to the next wave!
さあ 無限大の可能性の先へ
Come on, beyond infinite possibilities!
超電波バスターズ
Super Radio Wave Busters!
巡ってまるごと関わると
Spinning around and getting fully involved,
空の彼方へ おどれおどれ 超電波バスターズ
To beyond the sky! Dance, dance, Super Radio Wave Busters!
巡ってまるごと関わると
Spinning around and getting fully involved,
映像ナビゲーターにお任せ
Leave it to the video navigator!
インフィニティの先へ
Beyond infinity!
まだ見ぬ未来を ててててのれ
To a future yet unseen, te-te-te-te-no-re!
超電波バスターズ！
Super Radio Wave Busters!
透明する超感覚パリセン電波
Transparent, super-sensory Parisen radio waves!
アバンチュラリラリ トビコグ メリカナルバイノラー
Aventura-ri-ra-ri! Tobikogu merikanaru binaural!
アバンチュラリ 革命的電波
Aventura-ri! Revolutionary radio waves!
Tokino Soraと宇宙ハメて見せるニューワールド
Tokino Sora and the universe fitting together, showing a new world!
アバンチュラリラリ 一人じゃ行けないところまで
Aventura-ri-ra-ri! To places you can't go alone,
連れてきてくれてありがとう
Thank you for bringing me here!
Yeah!
さあ 時代を超えて
Come on, transcending time!
さあ 次はどこへ
Come on, where to next?
さあ 巡り続けるストーリーを駆け抜けて
Come on, running through the continuously revolving story!
超電波バスターズ 存在自体が君とのメモリー
Super Radio Wave Busters! Our very existence is a memory with you!
3, 2, 1 会いたい夢はここに
3, 2, 1, the dream I want to meet is right here!
今 僕らの物語が始まる
Now, our story begins!
超電波バスターズ 巡ってまるごと関わると
Super Radio Wave Busters! Spinning around and getting fully involved,
空の彼方へ おどれおどれ 超電波バスターズ
To beyond the sky! Dance, dance, Super Radio Wave Busters!
巡ってまるごと関わると
Spinning around and getting fully involved,
映像ナビゲーターにお任せ
Leave it to the video navigator!
インフィニティの先へ
Beyond infinity!
まだ見ぬ未来を ててててのれ
To a future yet unseen, te-te-te-te-no-re!
超電波バスターズ！
Super Radio Wave Busters!
Wow...
次元を超えて 理想の先へ 絶対超電波！
Transcending dimensions, beyond ideals, absolute super radio waves!
午前0時のトバリの町を
In the town veiled by midnight,
ひとりじめしている気分
I feel like I have it all to myself.
散らばったビル明かり
The scattered building lights,
失ったものばかりかき集めている
I'm just gathering up all the things I've lost.
目を閉じて踊ろう
Close your eyes and let's dance.
サヨナラって言わないし
I won't say goodbye,
永遠の夜なんてないのは分かってる
And I know there's no such thing as an eternal night.
だから
So...
君と明かす夜かい
Is this a night I spend with you?
明日もまた同じ
Even tomorrow, it's the same,
朝日が昇るなら
if the morning sun rises...
Woo-oh-oh-oh
何もない 暗く光る夜か
Is it a dark, glowing night with nothing else?
星空のミラーボール
A mirror ball in the starry sky,
Woo-oh-oh-oh
私を照らして
illuminate me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to shake the Earth with our tap dancing,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away right here.
午前5時の夜明けの街で
In the city at the dawn of 5:00 AM,
なんかひとりぼっちな気分
I somehow feel all alone.
薄まってゆくパレット ぼんやり眺める
I absently stare at the fading palette,
ベッドで期待している
sitting on the bed in anticipation
君の足音を
for the sound of your footsteps.
触れたくても 触れられないし
Even if I want to touch you, I can't,
運命の赤い糸なんて 知らないし
and I know nothing about red threads of fate.
それでも君と繋がっていたい
Even so, I want to stay connected with you.
明るくなる空に この思い乗せても
Even if I place these feelings into the brightening sky...
Woo-oh-oh-oh
何も見えない 灰色に流れる
I can see nothing, drifting into the grayness,
雲から差し込む
shining through the clouds...
Woo-oh-oh-oh
他人事なの？
Does it not concern you?
たっぷり深呼吸して
Taking a deep breath,
境界線を越える
I cross over the boundary line.
一番見える場所
To the place where I can see best,
裸足で踊る 夜空のまわり
dancing barefoot around the night sky,
キラキラ光るの
sparkling brightly.
ねぇ 早く気づいて
Hey, notice me quickly,
エスコートして
and escort me.
明日もまた同じ 朝日が昇るなら
Tomorrow, if the same morning sun rises again,
Woo-oh-oh-oh
何もない 暗く光る夜か
Is it a dark, glowing night with nothing else?
星空のミラーボール
A mirror ball in the starry sky,
Woo-oh-oh-oh
私を照らして
illuminate me.
タップで地球揺らすくらい
Enough to shake the Earth with our tap dancing,
ここで踊り明かそう
let's dance the night away right here.
Ah yeah...
「なんであなたにはできないの？」
"Why can't you do it?"
なんてさ 陰口言われたり呆れられたり
They talk behind my back or get exasperated with me,
「評価下がる」って言われて
telling me my evaluations will drop.
電車は私を置き去りにしちゃうし
The train leaves me behind,
葉物野菜もスピード早すぎだね
and even leafy vegetables spoil too quickly.
ありのままの素敵な
Just being wonderfully myself
努力だけじゃ足りないんだ ハイテク
and putting in effort isn't enough in this high-tech world.
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっとここまで連れてきたんだ
Working myself to death every day, I finally brought myself here.
あなたにはわからない
You wouldn't understand,
わかってほしくない
nor do I want you to understand.
私の苦労も このもどかしさもご存知ないで
Stay ignorant of my hardships and my frustration,
いてね
okay?
「きっとあなたにもできるはず」
"I'm sure you can do it too,"
なんてさ 言うほど無責任にはなりたくない
I don't want to be irresponsible enough to say things like that.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って賭ける値打ちはあると思った
Even so, I thought it was worth giving my absolute all to bet on it.
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like throwing in the towel,
でも諦めたくはない
but I don't want to give up.
私の未来も 失敗も全部私だけのもの
My future and my failures all belong solely to me.
あなたにはわからない
You wouldn't understand,
わかってほしくない
nor do I want you to understand.
私の苦労も このもどかしさもご存知ないで
Stay ignorant of my hardships and my frustration...
投げ出したくなるよ
I feel like throwing in the towel,
でも諦めたく...
but I don't want to give...
は言わない
...I won't say.
私の未来も
My future, too,
失敗も全部渡さないよ
and my failures—I won't give any of it away.
気づかない 気づかないフリして
Pretending not to notice, pretending not to notice,
可愛いだけの私でいい
it's fine for me to just be cute.
Yeah!
La la la la...
1, 2, 3!
胸に詰め込んだ
The dreams I've stuffed into my heart
夢はぐちゃぐちゃで
are all jumbled up,
勇気がいるけど
and though it takes courage,
君にだけは見せよう
I'll show them only to you.
横になろうかな
Shall we lie down side by side?
一筋縄いかない
It won't be simple or straightforward,
秘密の街を渡っていこう
but let's cross through this secret city.
深呼吸をして取った言葉
The words I spoke after taking a deep breath—
とっておきを誰にも渡さない
I won't hand my special prize to anyone.
最高のリズム
Even when the best rhythm
うまくいかない日だって
doesn't go well on some days,
強気で歌う
I'll sing out with confidence!
私の教科書 見ずに閉じたら
If I close my textbook without looking,
何だってやれそうだ
it feels like I can do anything!
落書きの中に光ってた
Glowing amidst the doodles,
想いを君とこうして交わし合えたなんて
to be able to share these feelings with you like this,
嘘みたいだな
feels like a dream!
もっと瞬いて印して
Sparkle more and leave your mark!
Yeah, high five!
夢も甘いも集めたの
I gathered dreams and sweetness.
試そうかな 成長できるかな
Shall I give it a try? Can I grow?
トモにバッチを
A badge for us together,
あーおー
Ah-Oh
サン！
3!
ダントツ上った
Rose far above the rest!
輪の中に一歩踏み出して
Stepping one step into the circle,
楽しかった日々 ほらいつのまに
look, before we knew it, those fun days
昨日よりも加速してる
are accelerating even faster than yesterday.
ちゃんと繋いで手
Hold my hand tightly.
簡単じゃないホームの
Though it's not easy, at home,
掛け声はいつも君が明るく放って支えてくれる
your cheerful calls always support me.
ずっと刻まれて光るよ
Engraved forever, it will keep shining.
水数えたら 砂に描いた絵
If I count the water, the drawing on the sand
消えてしまうけど それと同じで
fades away, but just like that,
君の顔ばかり浮かび出てたら
if only your face keeps coming to mind,
アイスみたいにとろけて
I melt away just like ice cream.
段々不可解になる
It's getting more and more incomprehensible.
夢も愛もキュッとしていっぱいだから
Squeezed full with dreams and love,
持ち切れない
I can't hold them all.
でも欲張りすぎてきっと閉じていく
But I'm too greedy, so it's sure to close up.
ラーラーラー チュッチュッ 恋に落ちちゃって
La la la, chu chu, falling in love,
チュッチュッ 戻れない
chu chu, I can't turn back.
あれあれ なんで ふわーりと 心が まだ 熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my heart still gently grow warm?
ラーラーラー チュッチュッ 君の重力で チュッチュッ 引き寄せて
La la la, chu chu, pulled in by your gravity, chu chu,
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで
like looking through a kaleidoscope,
ねぇ キラキラな 未来 見たい 分からない
hey, I want to see a sparkling future, I don't know.
アップアンドダウンで 超振り回す
Swinging all around with ups and downs,
要はね 今日はね 四六時中
in short, today, 24/7,
カレンダー30日じゃ足りない
a 30-day calendar isn't enough.
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do that, this, and everything!
キュンキュキュ上昇 ドキドキ白書
Heartbeat rising, heart-throbbing white paper,
キュンキュキュ降下 深呼吸
heartbeat dropping, deep breath.
キュンキュキュ上昇 ラブメーター
Heartbeat rising love meter,
キュンキュキュ降下 追撃戦
heartbeat dropping, pursuit battle!
無限大の愛だけど 失敗だけど 諦めない
It's infinite love, and I fail, but I won't give up,
まだ欲張りだから 君と閉じていく
because I'm still greedy, I'm closing in with you.
もう ラーラーラー チュッチュッ 心がハマって
Ah, la la la, chu chu, my heart is hooked,
チュッチュッ 抜け出せない
chu chu, I can't break free.
あれあれ なんで 目まぐるしい 心が まだ 熱くなるの
Oh my, why does my dizzying heart still grow warm?
ラーラーラー チュッチュッ スピード重視で チュッチュッ 引き寄せて
La la la, chu chu, focusing on speed, chu chu, pulling close,
カレイドスコープ 覗いてるみたいで
like looking through a kaleidoscope,
ねぇ キラキラな 未来 見たい 分からない
hey, I want to see a sparkling future, I don't know.
ちっぽけだな 理想を描く 私はまだ
So tiny, drawing my ideals, I am still...
未完成で あの空に 目を背けてしまうんだ
incomplete, turning my eyes away from that sky.
考えても どうしようもないことだとか
Things that can't be helped no matter how much I think,
透明な 心から 色々考えてくるけど
I keep pondering various thoughts from a transparent heart, but...
だからこそ 笑顔になれ
That's precisely why, smile!
だからこそ 負けないで
That's precisely why, don't lose!
羽ばたくための 羽を手にして
Obtaining wings to take flight,
飛び立っていくんだよ
I am soaring into the sky!
空を飛んで行こう 飛んで行こう 色づいていく夢 ほら 虹の空
Let's fly through the sky, fly through the sky, look, a rainbow sky of coloring dreams!
青 混ぜてみよう 混ぜてみよう 少し大きくなったね
Let's try mixing in blue, mixing it in, it grew a little bigger, didn't it?
空は青色 青色 少し経ったら すぐに茜色
The sky is blue, blue, after a little while, soon a sunset red.
ちょっと迷っても 迷っても ゆっくり風を受けて
Even if I get a little lost, lost, gently receiving the wind.
空を飛んで行こう 飛んで行こう
Let me fly through the sky, fly through the sky!
空は青色 茜色
The sky is blue, sunset red.
君に願いを なんて行く先で いつしか 忘れていた 奇跡の過ごし方を
Wishing upon you, along the way, I forgot how to live miracles before I knew it.
ある時は 笑顔になれ ある時は 泣き顔で
Sometimes smiling, sometimes with a tearful face,
見上げた空を 目印にして 旅立っていくんだよ
using the sky I looked up at as a guide, setting off on my journey!
届け
Reach out!
ワン ツー
One, two!
雨の日の声
The voice on a rainy day,
空が青色 影の色
the sky is blue, the color of shadows.
心がずっと落ち込んでしまっても やがては瑠璃色 青色
Even if my heart remains down, eventually it turns lapis lazuli, blue.
私があっと晴れ晴れにしちゃうから それぞれの形の色
Because I'll surely make it clear and bright, colors of each shape,
無限大ね いつかまたこの場所で
they're infinite, aren't they? Someday again in this place,
どんな空色が見えるかな
what sky color will we be able to see?
Fly High
Magic Fly Me to the Sky
Fly Me to the Sky Fly Me to the Sky
空までも飛んでいこう 飛んでいこう
Let's fly up to the sky, fly away
色付きはじめた夢は止まらない
The dream that began to take color won't stop
もっと伝えよう 伝えよう
Let's convey it more, convey it
ラララ こんなメロディーで
La-la-la, with a melody like this
空は青色 青色
The sky is blue, blue
少し疲れたらすぐに癒される色
A color that instantly comforts when feeling tired
ちょっと寂しくて うつむき見る
Feeling a bit lonely, I look down
だけど温かい気持ち
But it brings a warm feeling
手を取り合って笑い合ってくれるから
Because you hold my hand and laugh with me
これからはもう私のこと心配しないで
From now on, please don't worry about me anymore
今日の日のうららかに歌いながら
Sing cheerfully of this day
空までも飛んでいこう 飛んでいこう
Let's fly up to the sky, fly away
バーチャル リアル どっち可愛い？
Virtual or real, which is cute?
バーチャル リアル どっちも可愛い！
Virtual or real, both are cute!
Check it, Chu, Chu, Chu, Chu...
Cherry, Cherry, Chu, Chu, Chu...
サムネタップ初めまして キュンキュンてしたならハート押して
Tap thumbnail, nice to meet you; heart fluttered? Like!
通知はオン いつでもウェルカム 一緒に踊ろうよ アーネノン
Turn notifications on, always welcome, dance together
お菓子食べたいけれどダイエット中 君の好みにアップデート中
Want sweets but on a diet, updating to your taste
ポチッと更新 君と更新 もっと推してほしいの
Click to update, update with you, support me more!
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual or real, which do you like?
繋がってる 1, 2, 3次元 1, 2, 3 で飛び越えて
Connected across 1D, 2D, 3D, leap across with 1, 2, 3
今やネットもリアルです チクチクしないで ラブとピースで
Net is real too, don't be harsh, love and peace
ちっくたっく わわわ ときめいちゃう ときかけガール
Tick-tock, wa-wa-wa, heart fluttering time-leaping girl
つぎたすリビングは 待てれば最強
The living space we build together is unbeatable
バーチャリアル
VirtuReal
Check it, Chu, Chu, Chu, Chu...
Cherry, Cherry, Chu, Chu, Chu...
2倍 swipe to be キュンキュンてしたなら手たたいて
Double swipe to be, if heart fluttered, clap hands!
アンチ勢も エンジョイ勢も 一緒に踊ろうよ アーネノン
Antis and fans alike, let's dance together
界隈一等だけどコラボ中 超楽しいことリサーチ中
Top in the scene, collaborating, researching fun stuff
ピピピ テレパシー 今日も配信 もっとハマってほしいの
Telepathy, streaming today too, get hooked more!
ねえねえ どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which is cute?
どっち可愛い？
Which is cute?
どっち可愛い？ どっち可愛い？
Which is cute? Which is cute?
どっち可愛い？
Which is cute?
ねえねえ どっち可愛い？ どっち可愛い？ どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which is cute? Which is cute?
どっち可愛い？ どっち可愛い？ どっち可愛い？
Which is cute? Which is cute?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけれどダイエット中 君の好みにアップデート中
Want sweets but on a diet, updating to your taste
ポチッと更新 君と更新 もっと推してほしいの
Click to update, update with you, support me more!
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？ バーチャル リアル どっちも好き！
Virtual or real, which do you like? I like both!
繋がってる 1, 2, 3次元 1, 2, 3 で飛び越えて
Connected across 1D, 2D, 3D, leap across with 1, 2, 3
今やネットもリアルです チクチクしないで ラブとピースで
Net is real too, don't be harsh, love and peace
ちっくたっく わわわ ときめいちゃう ときかけガール
Tick-tock, wa-wa-wa, heart fluttering time-leaping girl
つぎたすリビングは 待てれば最強
The living space we build together is unbeatable
バーチャリアル
VirtuReal
Check it, Chu, Chu, Chu, Chu...
Cherry, Cherry, Chu, Chu, Chu...
しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a moment.
2025.10.1 Wed
8th Anniversary
with DJ ANKIMO
ARE YOU READY?
8th Starry Bloomin' Anniversary Party
降り注ぐ青い雨に
In the pouring blue rain,
始まりを告げるチャイム
a chime signals the beginning.
本当は震えている
In truth, I am trembling,
手足が隠せないよ
unable to hide my shaking hands and feet.
物語の先はもう
The rest of the story is,
くじけない気持ちのこと
about an unyielding heart,
諦められなかったこと
and the things I could not give up on.
燕みたいに速く
If only I could fly as fast
飛べたらいいのに
as a swallow.
もう何もいらないから
Because I need nothing else,
忘れさせてよ
just let me forget.
どこまでも遠くへ行こう
Let's go as far away as possible,
届かなくてもいいの
even if we never reach it.
だからお願い
So please,
涙を拭くように
as if wiping away my tears,
あの闇を超えて
crossing beyond that darkness,
秘密の翼で
with secret wings,
みんなー！
Everyone!
隠した鍵は見つかった？
Did you find the hidden key?
それとも引き出しじゃなかった？
Or was it not in the drawer?
いつのまにか過ぎていた
Before I knew it, time had passed,
君のスペシャルな夢のつづき
the continuation of your special dream.
子供みたいに青く
If only I could wish with innocent purity,
願えたらいいのに
like a child.
色づく世界
A world taking on color,
檻の中で
inside a cage.
手のぬくもりで生きていたって
Even if we live by the warmth of our hands,
僕らの不安
our anxiety,
愛おしいものだから
is something precious.
間違えても 彷徨っても
Even if we make mistakes or wander,
探さないでよ
don't look for me.
空の果て
To the edge of the sky,
ずっとこの先を見つめて
gazing far ahead all the while.
飛び立つの
I will take flight,
この命かけて
staking my very life.
どこまでも遠くへ
Farther and farther away
ありのままの自分で
As my true self
涙を追い風に
Turning my tears into a tailwind
幾つもの夜を超えて
Overcoming countless nights
行こう 有限のこの空へ
Let's go to this finite sky
ららら...
La la la...
高鳴る胸に 祈りを乗せて
Placing a prayer upon my throbbing chest,
曖昧な夢を描く
I paint a vague dream.
幻想は想像のまま
An illusion cannot end
終われないんだ
as a mere fantasy.
答えを永遠と探し続けてて
Constantly searching for an answer for eternity,
何者かに成りたくて
wishing to become someone.
燦々と降る夕立を
The sudden evening rain pouring down intensely,
ただただ願った
I simply wished for it.
優しく寄り添って
Nestling gently beside me,
心が晴れるのならば
if it can clear my heart,
翼が生えたような気がして
I feel as if I've grown wings,
いつだって隣に居たから
because you were always right by my side.
だって 言葉に出来ないことが
Because the things I couldn't express in words
私の証明だ
are the proof of who I am.
世界にあふれ出た
Overflowing into the world,
愛しささえも言葉にして
putting even this fondness into words,
路地裏に咲いた花のように
like a flower blooming in a back alley,
世界を照らす
illuminating the world,
小さな光にあこがれて
longing for that small light.
名前を持たないまま咲け
Bloom without even having a name.
神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge us,
ひとつ ひとつ 枯れない花のように
one by one, like flowers that never wither.
昨日の自分にさようならして
Saying goodbye to who I was yesterday,
こぼれた涙
the tears that spilled over,
うまく笑えないけれど
even if I can't smile properly,
いつかは
someday...
だって 理想は遠ざかっていくばかり
Because my ideals keep drifting further away,
もう届かないよ
I can't reach them anymore.
どれだけ手を伸ばして
No matter how far I reach,
叫んだって届かないの
no matter how I shout, it won't reach.
どこでもない姿だとしても
Even if I'm a shape that belongs nowhere,
信じてる
I still believe.
どうか 歌よ響いて
Please, let my song resonate!
私の物語はまだ途中さ
My story is still just beginning!
行き止まりばかり足がすくんで
Paralyzed by constant dead ends,
立って居られないよ
I can't even stay standing.
音のない世界から
From a world without sound,
君を見つけて
I found you,
連れ出すんだ
and brought you out.
言葉紡いで歌うことが
Weaving words together to sing
私の運命だ
is my destiny.
世界にあふれ出た
Overflowing into the world,
愛しささえも言葉にして
putting even this fondness into words,
路地裏に咲いた花のように
like a flower blooming in a back alley,
願いを照らす
illuminating our wishes,
小さな光にあこがれて
longing for that small light.
いつか二人で晴れた空へ
Someday, together, into the clear blue sky.
のぼって
Climb up,
地球上
all across the globe,
どこどこどこどこ どこでも行けちゃう
anywhere, everywhere, we can go anywhere!
アバンチュール
Adventure!
あっという間に時代をぐるり
In the blink of an eye, wrapping around the eras,
のぼり
climbing up,
宇宙を走らせたら
if we race across the universe,
時代を妄想して
daydreaming about the ages,
サイボーグの波へ
into the wave of cyborgs.
さあ 無限大の可能性へ
Come, toward infinite possibilities!
飛んで
Soaring high,
Fly!
超電導
Superconductivity!
どこどこどこどこ どこだの
Where, where, where, where, wherever we are,
カラフルな世界を踊る
dancing through a colorful world.
超電導
Superconductivity!
巡って どこどこどこっと
Traveling around, wherever it takes us,
ここから未来を咲かせて
making the future bloom from right here,
インフィニティの先へ
beyond infinity!
騒ぎのモーションで 全力ダンスダンスダンス
With exciting motions, full power dance, dance, dance!
まだ見ぬ世界へ 飛んで飛んで飛んで それ！
To worlds yet unseen, jump, jump, jump, here we go!
超電導！
Superconductivity!
共鳴する 超科学的サンデー
Resonating super-scientific Sunday!
アバンチュール
Adventure!
飛び込む ケミカルパイの
Diving into the chemical pie,
ライブ！
Live!
アバンチュール
Adventure!
発見！ 連鎖 連鎖 さらに連動して 見せるわ
Discovery! Chain reaction after chain reaction, linking together, I'll show you!
アバンチュール
Adventure!
ひとりじゃ行けないところまで
To places I couldn't go all on my own.
行って 見て 見て 見て！
Go and look, look, look!
イエイ！ 見ててね！
Yeah! Keep watching!
さあ 時代を超えて
Come, transcending time!
さあ キワの声
Come, hear the voices on the edge,
さあ 巡り続く現象と希望
come, continuing phenomenon and hope,
届けて
reach out!
超電導
Superconductivity!
繋ぐエネルギーが 君との目をびびっ
The connecting energy sparks between our eyes,
一生分みたいな夢がここにインプレ
a lifetime's worth of dreams impress upon us right here,
爆上がりはじめた
starting to surge intensely,
トワの鍵へ
toward the key of eternity!
超電導
Superconductivity!
どこどこどこどこ どこだの
Where, where, where, where, wherever we are,
カラフルな世界を踊る
dancing through a colorful world.
超電導
Superconductivity!
巡って どこどこどこっと
Traveling around, wherever it takes us,
ここから未来を走らせ
letting the future race from right here,
インフィニティの先へ
beyond infinity!
騒ぎのモーションで 全力ダンスダンスダンス
With exciting motions, full power dance, dance, dance!
まだ見ぬ世界へ 飛んで飛んで飛んで それ！ 更新ね！
To worlds yet unseen, jump, jump, jump, here we go! Time to update!
限界を飛び越えて
Leaping far beyond the limits,
どこまでも行こう
let me take you anywhere!
幻想の自由！
Freedom of fantasy!
はい！ みんな、こんばんはー！
Hi! Good evening, everyone!
みんなの声が大きすぎて
Everyone's voices are so loud...
オケが聞こえないレベルの
...that I couldn't even hear the backing track...
大歓声、ありがとう！
...what an amazing cheer, thank you!
ちょっと、一回静かにしてもらっちゃおうかにゃ？
Can I ask everyone to quiet down for a second?
にゃー！ にゃー！
Meow~! Meow~!
ということで、1年半ぶりのソロライなんですけど...
So, this is my first solo concert in a year and a half, but...
えー、ちょっと恒例のやつやっていいですか？
Umm, can I do that usual call-and-response routine?
みんなー！
Everyone!
って言うんで、「はーい」とか言ってください。いきますよ？
When I say that, please respond with "Yeah!" or something. Here we go!
男の子ー！
Boys!
ちょっと恥ずかしいかもしれない。ちょっと手だけ振ってもいいよ。
Some of you might be shy. Just waving your hands is fine too!
女の子ー！
Girls!
声聞こえた！ ありがとう！
I heard you! Thank you!
海外の方ー！
People from overseas!
すごい！
Awesome!
そして...
And...
そうだなあ...
Let's see...
「めっちゃ遠くから来たよ」って人！ 絶対自分が一番遠いみたいな人、いる？
Anyone who came from super far away? Like, "I definitely traveled the furthest"?
あ、でも海外の方かな？ ありがとうございます！
Ah, maybe that's the overseas fans? Thank you so much!
そして！
And then!
そうだね、未成年の方ー！
Right, minors / younger fans!
イェーイ！ ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
ではみんなで行くよ？
Now, let's do everyone together!
みんなー！
Everyone!
こっち側ー！
This side!
That side!
最後に...
And lastly...
全員！
Everybody!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、というわけでね、これがやりたかったんです、ずっと。
Alright! So yeah, I've wanted to do this for so long!
ヘイ！ あ、いち... ふふっ...
Hey! Ah, one... Hehe...
というわけでですね、なんと...
So, as it turns out...
YouTubeで見ている皆さん、無料配信は...
To everyone watching on YouTube, the free stream...
ここまでなんです！ え〜 今来たばっかり？ 私も今来たばっかり！
ends here! Eh~ You just got here? I just got here too!
そうだよね、分かる分かる！
I know, right? I totally get it!
え〜 分かってるよ、コメントの皆んなも見えてるよ！
Eh~ I know, I can see everyone in the comments too!
イェーイって言ってるな〜 ちょっとラグってるのかもしれない
They're saying 'Yay~'! Maybe there's a bit of lag.
今来たばっかりって書いてね！ よろしく！
Be sure to comment 'I just got here!', okay? Thanks!
続きは、見たい人... 概要欄から...
If you want to watch the rest... from the description...
見てもらえると... どこにあるんだろう...？
if you could check it out... Where is it though...?
どこかに概要欄が多分あるんで、ここら辺からちょっと見てもらえれば嬉しいです！
There's probably a description somewhere around here, so I'd be happy if you checked it out!
ヤバっ...
Oh no...
次の曲行っちゃおうかな？
Shall we move on to the next song?
まだまだ盛り上がれる？
Can you guys get even more hyped?
みんながおうちにかえってくるの、待ってたよ！
I was waiting for everyone to come home!
というわけで！ 次の曲は、新アルバムからこの曲です！
So with that! The next song from my new album is this track!
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。★ライブチケット購入はコチラ▶▶ SPWN
[Text: The free stream preview ends here. ★Buy live tickets here ▶▶ SPWN]
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The free preview stream ends here.